swagster.com 2009-04-16

# Swagster.com - image hosting & music trading

This privacy statement covers the Swagster website (www.Swagster.com).

This privacy statement is limited to personal information (referred to as "information").

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us using this form : Swagster.com contact form.

**Information Collection and Use**

_**Information Collection**_

Swell Deal Enterprises LLC is the sole owner of the information collected through the Swagster.com. Swell Deal Enterprises LLC collects information from users at several different points. 

**_Surveys & Contests_**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as age). Contact information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes or otherwise in accordance with the Terms and Conditions of each competition or survey. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of improving the use of this site. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use 'users' information for any other purposes. 

**_Cookies_**

A cookie is information that a web site puts on the hard disk so that it can use it at a later time. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site, however, the cookie is associated with your user login and authentication on our server. Swell Deal Enterprises LLC has no ability to supervise, control or record your activity.

We do not store your name, your email address, your username or any other personally identifiable data in the cookie. Some of our business partners (advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. The information collected and the uses to which that information can be put are set out in our partners' privacy policies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.Swagster.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**_Log Files_**

Like most Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not collect personal information from logfiles. IP addresses are not kept after the statistics are logged in the aggregated database.

**Information Use**

**_Newsletter_**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter they can enter their email address within a form on the Swagster.com web site. Out of respect for users' privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. We will never send non-site related unsolicited marketing (spam), and will not sell or disclose our email database with non-Swell Deal Enterprises LLC companies.

**_Technical Announcements_**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out technical announcements. For instance, if the Swagster.com website is temporarily unavailable we might send users an email. These emails are not promotional in focus but may include advertising to cover the cost of sending.

**Disclosure of Information**

**_Legal Disclaimer_**

We may need to disclose personal information if required by law. For example, to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process. 

**_Aggregate Information_** (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This does not include any personally identifiable information. 

**_Business Transitions_**

In the event Swell Deal Enterprises LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, 'users' information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via prominent notice on www.Swagster.com for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of information of users held by Swell Deal Enterprises LLC. If as a result of the business transition, information will be used for a purpose different from that stated, or implied, at the time of collection users will be given a choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

**_Security_**

We take every reasonable precaution to protect information from misuse, loss and unauthorised access. Although we cannot guarantee that users' information will not be subject to unauthorised access by hackers, we have appropriate security procedures in place to protect 'users' information. Information is stored on secure, password protected servers and is only accessible by employees who need the information to perform a specific job. All employees are kept up to date on our security and privacy practices.

**_Updating Personal Information_**

Users may gain access to information that has by requesting it using this form: http://www.swagster.com/profile_menu.php. If a user's information changes such as email address, or if a user no longer desires email announcements or news letters, we provide a way to correct and update users' information. Users have a responsibility to tell us if their information changes as that is the only way we can ensure information is kept accurate and up to date. 

**_Notification of Changes_**

Swell Deal Enterprises LLC(Swagster.com) reserves the right to change this policy without prior written notice. It is a users responsibility to periodically check the privacy policy and terms and conditions for changes. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us using this form : http://www.swagster.com/contact_admin.php
